Her web connects them all.
Madame Web is a action, fantasy film directed by S.J. Clarkson.
Forced to confront revelations about her past, paramedic Cassandra Webb forges a relationship with three
young women destined for powerful futures...if they can all survive a deadly present.
Cassandra Webb, played by Dakota Johnson.
Julia Cornwall, played by Sydney Sweeney.
Anya Corazón, played by Isabela Merced.
Mattie Franklin, played by Celeste O'Connor.
Ezekiel Sims, played by Tahar Rahim.
O'Neil, played by Mike Epps.
Madame Web is a 2024 American superhero film
featuring the character from Marvel Comics.
It is the fourth film in Sony's Spider-Man Universe (SSU).
Dakota Johnson stars as the titular character, alongside Sydney Sweeney, Isabela Merced,
Celeste O'Connor, Tahar Rahim, Mike Epps, Emma Roberts, and Adam Scott.
The film was directed by S.
Clarkson from a screenplay she wrote with Claire Parker alongside
the writing team of Matt Sazama and Burk Sharpless.
The film depicts the origin story of Cassie Webb (Johnson), who confronts her past while trying to save three young women (Sweeney,
Merced, O'Connor) from Ezekiel Sims (Rahim), who wants to kill them before they become Spider-Women in the future and kill him.
Sony Pictures began developing a Madame Web film for its shared universe by
September 2019, with Sazama and Sharpless writing the script.
Clarkson joined as the director in May 2020, in her feature film
directorial debut, and Johnson was cast in early 2022.
Further castings occurred in the following months,
particularly for the Spider-Women characters.
Filming began in mid-July 2022 and wrapped before the end of the year,
occurring throughout Massachusetts, New York City, and Mexico.
Clarkson and Parker's involvement as writers was revealed in November 2023.
Johan Söderqvist, a frequent collaborator of
Clarkson, composed the film's score.
Madame Web premiered at the Regency Village Theatre in Westwood, Los Angeles, on February 12, 2024, and was
released in the United States two days later by Columbia Pictures via Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film was panned by critics and was a box-office bomb, grossing $100.5
million worldwide against a net production budget of $80 million.
It received three Golden Raspberry Awards: Worst Picture, Worst
Actress (for Johnson), and Worst Screenplay.
The film explores themes of new york city, spider,
based on comic, teenage girl, super power.